The only item, too, is the presentation by Ryan Varchie for all of the right.
Hi, Chief.
Good morning.
Thank you for this time.
I thank you for each person here.
I ask Father to be with the Council and Leaders of the City of Citizens.
I may well be in your will, Father.
I ask that you to watch over the employees, protect them.
I thank you for the season that we can celebrate and be thanksgiving for the country
and we live in.
I apologize to each other as they played and keep them safe.
I thank you for your side of Jesus Christ.
That's him.
And his name won't break anything.
Okay.
Please, sir.
We will do it in place, okay.
Okay.
I pray we just do it live at the United States of America and if you do it public for
Worcestersands, one nation under God in the Day of the Earth will lead to an impact as a star.
Okay, we are going to skip item 4 for now.
Item 5 is a couple of hidden redundant schedule personal period.
The only item was just to address the authority on the agenda.
There would be none item 6 can send it to the staff as recommending item 7 through 10 to the consent agenda.
I'm going to pull out item 9 because there are 10 and it's just 1 to 100 for a minute.
So, how about item 7 and 8 and 9?
Do we have a motion to approve item 7, 8, 9 as part of the consent agenda?
1, 2 and a second.
Second.
Johnson.
Wester.
Alright.
Lewis.
I'm Schultz.
And I just, our meeting schedule is nothing changing next year.
Everything is still at the same time.
What's up?
Third meeting.
And I plan to add a couple of days ago.
I didn't look at it closely.
We'll get out of our work sessions scheduled for four or five or two days or everything else.
We've made no change.
For the council.
Right.
Four.
We changed it to 430 and so that's how I had done the next year schedule for 2018.
For the work session.
Yes.
From 4 to 430.
Okay.
All right.
Thank you.
Okay.
So, do we have motion to approve the 2018 schedule for the issue?
Motion to approve.
Any second?
No second.
Roll call please.
Wester.
Johnson.
Lewis.
I.
Forster.
Shultz.
I.
Any new business?
To have reports on your packet.
If there are no questions.
We have any trustee community announcements.
Okay.
We are going to.
You think that.
You're on the way.
So we're going to recess this meeting.
And we are going to.
We're going to.
We're going to call the water.
The.